Hello
What have you been doing lately?
Resistance
I have with me three letters to you
I have no special requirements
As long as it's a purebred, submissive, Holocaust -denied girl
that takes care of the household
Amen she might be something
Well
Note the picture got much darker when I scanned it, she writes
Aa, you hope that
mm
Eh, she is not convicted of incitement against people group
Mm, there is a little PK warning on it
Is that it?
It is it, mm
It's hard, you don't want to get too dear and lose focus
In the fight against the traitor of the Jewish conspiracy
Thank you
You are welcome
I appreciate the gift
Adde (?) Got similar by Eva
You wrote well in the letter
But you did not send with any family tree
Oh, eh
Sorry
And you wrote that you are not Nazi
But is interested in it?
Yes, I get so incredibly inspired when I heard you talk about persecution of homosexuals
and expulsion of racial stamps and dissent
She probably has a little Nazi in herself anyway that girl
So, would you be prepared to move home to me and
do some Nazi stuff?
Yeah i think it might suit me
Johan makes me feel like I was in the Third Reich
I want to meet Johan because he seems aggressive and hotful
I hope I get the chance
to bring his violent genes on
Aa